export const data = [
  {
    question: " What percentage of DNA a chimpanzee shares with human?",
    answers: ["98%", "12%", "0%", "50%"],
    answer: "98%",
  },
  {
    question: "What is the loudest animals in the world?",
    answers: ["Gorilla", "Tiger", "Sper  whale", "Giraffe"],
    answer: "Sper whale",
  },
  {
    question: " What is the friendliest animal in the world?",
    answers: ["Dog", "Horse", "Pigeon", "Capybara"],
    answer: "Capybara",
  },
  {
    question: "Which one can taste with their feet?",
    answers: ["Elephants", "Butterflies", "Snails", "Birds"],
    answer: "Butterflies",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Under the sleepy eyes, it sits the nose of a super-detective, with a sense of smell up to a million times more sensitive than that of humans - what?",
    answers: ["Bloodhound", "Horse", "Rhino", "Cow"],
    answer: "Bloodhound",
  },
  {
    question:
      "By some estimates, eagles can see at least what times as much detail as humans?",
    answers: ["8 times", "10 times", "4 times", "5 times"],
    answer: "4 times",
  },
  {
    question: "What is Columbidae?",
    answers: ["Bird", "Insect", "Reptile", "Lizard"],
    answer: "Bird",
  },
  {
    question: "In the wild, how many years a pigeon can live?",
    answers: ["8 years", "6 years", "3 years", "4 years"],
    answer: "6 years",
  },
  {
    question: "Hedwig animal was found in which movie?",
    answers: ["Tarzan", "Lord of the Rings", "Harry Potter", "A Whisker Away"],
    answer: "Harry Potter",
  },
  {
    question: "Electroreception skills are shown by which creature?",
    answers: ["Sharks", "Saola", "Ti-Liger", " Seneca White Deer"],
    answer: "Sharks",
  },
];
